My Perfect Romance is a romance, tv movie film directed by Justin G. Dyck.
Newly appointed CEO of Robinson Tech, Wes Robinson, is looking
for new ideas to boost the company's sales.
Vivian Blair, a program developer, shares a dating algorithm
she has been working on called My Perfect Match.
Wes sees potential and an opportunity to turn the
company around and launches the service.
When the pair is challenged to use My Perfect Match themselves to find
love, this algorithm shows some interesting results.
Vivian Blair, played by Kimberly-Sue Murray.
Wes, played by Christopher Russell.
Michelle Blair, played by Jodie Sweetin.
Adele, played by Lauren Holly.
Ms. Robinson, played by Morgan Fairchild.
George, played by Josh Dean.
My Perfect You is a 2018 Philippine romantic drama film directed by Cathy
Garcia-Molina from a story and screenplay written by Carmi G.
Raymundo, with Molina and Kristine C.
Gabriel as co-writers of the latter.
The film stars Gerald Anderson and Pia Wurtzbach and tells the story of a man who's
down in the dumps and a woman who helps him see the light again.
The supporting cast includes Dimples Romana, Tonton
Gutierrez, Janus del Prado, and Wilma Doesnt.
Produced and distributed by Star Cinema, the film was
theatrically released on March 14, 2018.
The tone is emotional.